<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UNO on ETdoFresh</title>
    <link>/tags/uno/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UNO on ETdoFresh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 19:30:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/uno/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Measuring Presence and Performance in a Virtual Reality Police Use of Force Training Simulation Prototype</title>
      <link>/measuring-presence-and-performance-in-a-virtual-reality-police-use-of-force-training-simulation-prototype/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 19:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/measuring-presence-and-performance-in-a-virtual-reality-police-use-of-force-training-simulation-prototype/</guid>
      <description>In this paper we describe a virtual reality training simulation designed to help police officers learn use of force policies. Our goal is to test a training simulation prototype by measuring improvements to presence and performance. If successful, this can lead to creating a full-scale virtual reality narrative training simulation. The simulation uses a planner-based experience manager to determine the actions of agents other than the participant. Participants’ actions were logged, physiological data was recorded, and the participants filled out questionnaires.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Camelot</title>
      <link>/camelot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 19:11:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/camelot/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Police Use of Force Simulation</title>
      <link>/police-use-of-force-simulation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 19:14:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/police-use-of-force-simulation/</guid>
      <description>I am the primary Unity developer on the Police Use of Force Prototype Simulation. It is a research project I’ve worked on with the Narrative Intelligence Laboratoryat the University of New Orleans. You control a Police Officer in either VR or Keyboard/Mouse controls learning Use of Force policies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honest Abe</title>
      <link>/honest-abe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 15:59:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/honest-abe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honest Abe is an arcade beat-em up style game about good ol’ President Lincoln. The confederates stole Mary Todd and beat our hero up and left him for dead. But he’s not dead, and he’s out for revenge!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sokoban</title>
      <link>/sokoban/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 19:20:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/sokoban/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ninja-Time Strategy!</title>
      <link>/intro-to-ninja-time-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2014 07:58:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/intro-to-ninja-time-strategy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This game is quite different. It’s not one of those games I’ve been dying to make for many years. On the flip-side, I decided to try to make a game on a “whim”. I also was very interested in HTML5 before I started, so this was a perfect opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guerra</title>
      <link>/intro-to-guerra/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 07:19:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/intro-to-guerra/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guerra is Spanish for War! This was the title of a childhood game that I used to play with my friends. It was a mixture between action and the game of Memory.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>