<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal on ETdoFresh</title>
    <link>/categories/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal on ETdoFresh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:09:26 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Check In – Start of Fall 2019</title>
      <link>/check-in-start-of-fall-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 00:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/check-in-start-of-fall-2019/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been on a bit of an emotional roller coaster this Summer. I’m back on the ground. I’m dizzy. I’m trying to get my right footing, but stumbling a bit…. but here I am. Able and willing!
Be present…. be present….. be present!
One of the things about this life, if you don’t pay attention, this life will pass you by. When you get stuck doing the same thing, day-in and day-out, time flashes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 April Progress Report</title>
      <link>/2019-april-progress-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 01:13:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019-april-progress-report/</guid>
      <description>March has been a trip! Here’s my March:
 Started the month off with a little NOLA vacation, aka the Mardi Gras 2019. Work has been interesting as I’ve been transitioning away from a project that I never really wanted in the first place. So, excited about that… but I do not know how long this “transition” will last. GDC 2019! Wow! What a cool experience. Many like minded game makers all meeting in one place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 March Progress Report</title>
      <link>/2019-march-progress-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 06:20:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019-march-progress-report/</guid>
      <description>Alright, definitely slowed down this February. Still doing alright, but I got sick for about 10 days , and then sprained my ankle. So training has been bad the second half of the month!
 Submitted my camera ready version of my Police Use of Force paper! Woot! Been on autopilot mostly, doing the work/school thing… Homeworks, projects, programming, etc. Completed a simple 3d project this weekend that I’ve been wanting to do for a little while now!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019 February Progress Report</title>
      <link>/2019-february-progress-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 04:25:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019-february-progress-report/</guid>
      <description>2019 is off to a great start. I think I’ll just list out good stuff, and then list out what I should focus on this month.
 Did all my training runs/jogs for Crescent City Classic Been keeping track of my input calories into my body using MyFitnessPal  Lost ~6-7lbs in the process of the above   Planned or planning various trips  GDC [indie pass] in March 2019 @ San Francisco FLAIRS-32 in May 2019 @ Saratosa, FL  (OMG, my paper got accepted, I get to go somewhere!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Close of 2018</title>
      <link>/close-of-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 04:21:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/close-of-2018/</guid>
      <description>Another year in the books! Time to reflect and time to look forward…
Mirror, mirror of the year… Here are some of the key things I remember from this year…
 2018 started with some intense biking for about 2 weeks Mardi Gras spent with my prima Pilly, her family, tia Patty, and tio Gabriel  Experienced my first car break in with the family Really enjoyed the sharing of our feelings at the family table with drinks, laughter, and tears   Ran the Crescent City Classic with a bad time of ~1:20hr Played many, many Racquetball games with my friends Cut my long hair!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Checking In!</title>
      <link>/checking-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 04:14:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/checking-in/</guid>
      <description>So it’s been a while…
I switched gears, trying to find a calling that fits me. I’m still programming of course! I even got a job as a programmer in January! Woot! But my hobby is what drives me. I stopped working on the network physics engine and I started working on a vector animation software targeted for tablets. I feel like with this project I can finish in a semester and it can be a tool that can help game devs everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>