<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ghost on ETdoFresh</title>
    <link>/tags/ghost/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ghost on ETdoFresh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 06:38:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/ghost/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Hugo</title>
      <link>/moving-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 06:38:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/moving-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Oh man. I&amp;rsquo;ve been putting so many hours trying to figure out how to move my blog over to Hugo/GitHub. I&amp;rsquo;m getting very close. I found a tool, WordPress to Hugo Exporter, which will hopefully get me going. I copied my WordPress site locally (here&amp;rsquo;s how), and now I&amp;rsquo;m running&amp;hellip;
/var/www/html/wp-content/plugins/wordpress-to-hugo-exporter# mkdir tmp php hugo-export-cli.php ./tmp It just finished! Nice! Well, all my blog posts are over I think? Now I just have to spend hours formatting them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving from Ghost to Hugo</title>
      <link>/moving-from-ghost-to-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2020 10:13:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/moving-from-ghost-to-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Introduction After 1 or 2 days, I realized slimming down from WordPress to Ghost was just the beginning. I was somewhat satisfied. However, after setting up comments and looking at other integrations for Ghost, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m just using a mini/less functional WordPress. The markdown editing was the reason I made the switch, but then I realized, I might as well just scrap the database backend and keep all the files in a repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Ghost on Linode Docker</title>
      <link>/install-ghost-on-linode-docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 22:23:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/install-ghost-on-linode-docker/</guid>
      <description>Hi! Here are the steps I took to install Ghost on a Linode.
Create a &amp;ldquo;Docker&amp;rdquo; Linode. Give it a few minutes to spin up.
Before I got started, I went ahead and made sure my domain was setup correctly in Linode.
And make sure your SOA Record and A/AAAA Record are accurate (and pointed to your Linode&amp;rsquo;s IP Address)
Log into your Linode and create these folders where settings and persistent data should be stored.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Increase Maximum File Size Server Allows</title>
      <link>/increase-maximum-file-size-server-allows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/increase-maximum-file-size-server-allows/</guid>
      <description>When setting up a blog server, as we did in Install Ghost on Linode Docker, you may have realized that sometimes the server does not like huge files. In order to up the maximum file size allowed, edit your ~/nginx-conf/default.conf
server { ... client_max_body_size 500M; } Then restart your, in this site&amp;rsquo;s case
docker exec -it $DOCKER_POD_ID service nginx restart References https://etdofresh.com/install-ghost-on-linode-docker/
https://www.tecmint.com/limit-file-upload-size-in-nginx/</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>